{
    "subject": "resource/Ezzatabad,_Khoy",
    "predicate": "ontology/isPartOf",
    "object": "resource/Central_District_(Khoy_County)",
    "human_readable": "Ezzatabad, Khoy is part of the Central District (Khoy County).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9827306866645813,
            "question": "Name the district that Ezzatabad, Khoy belongs to."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9821235537528992,
            "question": "What district is Ezzatabad, Khoy part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9702858328819275,
            "question": "Is Ezzatabad, Khoy part of a specific district?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9534489512443542,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Ezzatabad, Khoy and the Central District?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9471390843391418,
            "question": "Where is Ezzatabad, Khoy located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7743290066719055,
            "question": "What is the administrative division of Ezzatabad, Khoy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7163453102111816,
            "question": "In which county is the Central District situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6615771651268005,
            "question": "What is the name of the county that includes the Central District?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.657230019569397,
            "question": "To which county does the Central District belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.563551127910614,
            "question": "Is the Central District a part of a larger county?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ezzatabad, Khoy is part of the Central District (Khoy County).",
            "html": "dbpedia_173_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which county does the Central District belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_173_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the county that includes the Central District?",
            "html": "dbpedia_173_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which county is the Central District situated?",
            "html": "dbpedia_173_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_173_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_173_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_173_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_173_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_173_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_173_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_173_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_173_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_173_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_173_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement. Specifically, it mentions \"Ezzatabad\" as a village in the \"Central District of Khoy County, West Azerbaijan Province, Iran.\" This aligns with the query stating that Ezzatabad is part of the Central District (Khoy County)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}